Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 806
    - Local 806 Newspaper Clippings, November 1, 1940-December 12, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Dayton Journal, December 12, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Leaflet, "Resolution", December 11, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Local 806 Wood Bar Industry Wages, December 23, 1940-January 8, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to Research Department, December 23, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Kirkendall, January 8, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Staff Application Leath, March 25-29, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to James Matles, March 25, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Kirkendall, March 29, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Dayton Steel Foundry Strike, March 9-July 3, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to James Matles, March 9, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Krikendall, March 26-April 9, 1941; 2-3.
      - Kirkendall to John Steelman, July 3, 1941; 4.
    - Local 806 GHR Foundry Conversion, November 3, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to Edward Keenan, November 3, 1941; 1.
      - Kirkendall to James Matles, November 3, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Suspended Members, November 6-10, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to James Matles, November 6, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Kirkendall, November 10, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Conscription, November 5-10, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - K.M. Kirkendall to James Matles with Contract Excerpt, November 5, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Kirkendall, November 10, 1941; 2.
    - Local 806 Correspondence, June 23, 1937-January 17, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - Charter Application, June 23, 1937; 1.
      - K.M. Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 26, 1941; 2.
      - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Education, December 2, 1941; 3.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Supplies, December 9, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Kirkendall Regarding Finances, April 11, 1941; 5.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Foreign Policy, November 13, 1941; 6.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Gondert and Lienesch Contracts, December 29, 1941; 7.
      - Kirkendall to Greg Hollreck Regarding Vocational Training, January 17, 1942; 8.
      - Kirkendall to McSherry Regarding Vocational Training, January 17, 1942; 9.
    - Local 806 Dayton Elite Machine Console Manufacturing Precision Tool and Die Company, July 19, 1937-August 22, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Local 806 Dayton Elite Machine Console Manufacturing Precision Tool and Die Company, July 2-November 29, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Local 807
    - Local 807 Officers Lists, August 1945 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Local 807 Membership Lists, February 11, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Local 807 Incoming Correspondence, June 19, 1941-December 11, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Julius Emspak to Glen Miller Regarding Materials, February 17, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Finances, October 11, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Fee Waiver, February 28, 1945-December 11, 1946; 3-4.
      - James Maltes to Walter Beare Regarding Acknowledged Information, June 19, 1941; 5.
      - Matles to Robert Bennett Regarding Acknowledged Letter, April 29, 1942; 6.
      - Matles to Bennett Regarding Plant Conditions, May 20, 1942; 7.
    - Local 807 Outgoing Correspondence, June 17, 1941-February 21, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - Walter Beare to James Matles Regarding Union Political Affrairs, June 17, 1941; 1.
      - Robert Bennett to Matles Regarding Organizational Work, April 21, 1942; 2.
      - Glenn Miller Letter Regarding Bonding, February 15, 1942; 3.
      - Miller to Julius Emspak Regarding Fee Waiver, February 21, 1945; 4.
    - Local 807 Bonding, February 21-24, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Local 807 Charter Requisition, December 14, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Local 807 Newspaper, NCR Union News, October 22, 1940-November 22, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Local 807 Pamphlet, NCR Local Opens Drive for Collective Bargaining (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Local 807 Organization, July 17, 1937-June 25, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      - Charter Application, July 17, 1937; 1.
      - Arthur Garfield to Julius Emspak, February 9, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Garfield, February 13, 1942; 3.
      - Garfield to James Matles, June 25, 1942; 4.
    - Local 807 Charter Reissuance, December 14-29, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      - Lem Markland to Julius Emspak, December 14, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Markland, December 17-29, 1948; 2-3.
    - Local 807 Dayton National Cash Register Workers, July 17, 1937-January 22, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Local 807 Dayton National Cash Register Workers, March 28, 1937-August 22, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Local 807 Correspondence, Henry Fiering to Julius Emspak, August 1945 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Local 236F
    - Local 236F Officers Lists, January 18, 1942-February 2, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Local 236F Incoming Correspondence, March 1, 1950-November 14, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 82)
      - Julius Emspak to Winfrey Duncan Regarding Veterans Dues, March 1, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Duncan Regarding Finances, April 28-May 11, 1950; 2-3.
      - Emspak to Lloyd James Regarding Strikes, September 19, 1950; 4.
      - Emspak to Thomas DeLong Regarding Strikes, October 19, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Sterling Neal Regarding Per Capita, December 18, 1950; 6.
      - Emspak to Utley Vincent Regarding Strikes, September 8-October 1, 1952; 7-11.
      - Emspak to William Overby Regarding Strikes, October 2, 1952; 12.
      - Emspak to Vincent Regarding Strikes, October 7-November 14, 1952; 13-20.
    - Local 236F Incoming Correspondence, February 8, 1950-April 13, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      - Julius Emspak to Utley Vincent Regarding Strikes, November 21, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Vincent Regarding Finances, April 16, 1953; 2.
      - Emspak to WIlliam Overby Regarding Finances, September 3, 1953; 3.
      - Emspak to Kermit Phelps Regarding Per Capita, March 17, 1954; 4.
      - Emspak to James Robinson Regarding Finances, April 13, 1955; 5.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Overby Regarding Finances, October 8, 1952; 6.
      - Fitzgerald to Vincent Regarding Steward Class, January 29, 1953; 7.
      - John Gojack to Carl Keithley Regarding UE-FE Merger, February 8, 1950; 8.
      - James Matles to James Morris Regarding Strikes, March 12, 1952; 9.
      - Matles to Arthur Dlugoff Regarding Staff Members Strikes, November 5, 1952; 10.
      - Matles to Overby Regarding Strike, January 8, 1953; 11.
      - Nathaniel McKenzie to Local 236F Executive Board Regarding African American Strikes, February 18, 1952; 12.
      - Emma Meagher to Dlugoff Regarding Staff Members, November 17, 1952; 13.
      - David Ratner to Overby Regarding Finances, October 16, 1952; 14.
    - Local 236F Outgoing Correspondence, November 5, 1948-April 6, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      - Cris Gastinger to UE Regarding Labor Education, November 5, 1948; 1.
      - Sterling Neal to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 9, 1950; 2.
      - William Overby to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 30, 1952; 3.
      - Overby to Emspak Regarding Strikes, September 17, 1952; 4-5.
      - Overby to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 29, 1952; 6.
      - Overby to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes, October 8, 1952; 7.
      - Overby to Emspak Regarding Strikes, December 31, 1952; 8.
      - Overby to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 27, 1953; 9.
      - Kermit Phelps to David Ratner Regarding Finances, January 15, 1954; 10.
      - Phelps to Emspak Regarding Strikes, March 8-17, 1954; 11-12.
      - Phelps to Ratner Regarding Finances, January 18, 1955; 13.
      - James Robinson to Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Conference, March 23, 1954; 14.
      - Robinson to Neal Regarding Finances, April 6, 1955; 15.
      - Thomas Ruffing to Ratner Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 9, 1953; 16.
      - Utley Vincent to James Matles Regarding International Harvester Conference Board, February 8, 1952; 17.
      - Charles Yates to Emspak Regarding Finances and Per Capita, January 19, 1952; 18.
      - Yates to Emspak Regarding Strikes, March 20, 1952; 19.
      - Yates to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 20, 1952; 20.
    - Local 236F Finances, September 1952-March 1955 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      - Strike Expenses, September 1952; 1.
      - Legal Expenses, March 17, 1953; 2.
      - Per Capita Form, February-March 1955; 3.
    - Local 236F Leaflets, August 26-31, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 86)
      - "Keep Your Eye On the Ball" Regarding Unemployment, United Auto Workers Seniority and Inter-union Rivalry, August 26, 1953; 1.
      - "We Are Faced" Regarding Unemployment, African Americans and UAW Inter-union Rivalry, August 27, 1953; 2.
      - "Your Next Door Neighbor" Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry and Seniority, August 27, 1953; 3.
      - "Arbitration of Seniority Set For Today" Regarding Unemployment, August 31, 1953; 4.
      - "FE Members in Foundry" Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry, 5.
      - "Meeting Changed to Yount Hall", 6.
      - "First and Third Shift Votes Legal Strike", 7.
      - "Job Facts and Seniority In Foundry" Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry, 8.
      - Statement of Candidate For Office, 9.
    - Local 236F Pamphlets, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 87)
      - Over a Long Period Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 5, 1953; 1.
      - Statement on Lay-offs, August 24, 1953; 2.
      - The Harvester Lay-Off and Your Community, 1953; 3.
      - Program for Local 236 Regarding Unemployent, African Americans and Negotiations, 4.
    - Local 236F Newspaper Clippings, September 3, 1952-March 31, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 88)
      - "The Unions and the IHC", September 3, 1952; 1.
      - "Ten Union Men Are Fired By Harvester", March 31, 19853; 2.
      - "Strikes Over Two Suspensions Threaten Tie-Up of Harvester", 3.
    - Local 236F Press Release and Newspaper Clipping, April 7, 1950-October 1, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 89)
      - Press Release Regarding Negotiations and Arbitration, April 7, 1950; 1.
      - Cub, October 1, 1953; 2.
    - Local 236F United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 21, 1949-October 18, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      - Grant Oakes to James Matles, November 21, 1949; 1.
      - Robert Logsdon to Matles with Leaflet, July 10, 1950; 2.
      - Logsdon Memo, July 1950; 3.
      - Logsdon to Matles, July 14, 1950; 4.
      - Charles Wright to Jim, October 1950; 5.
      - Logsdon to Julius Emspak, October 18, 1950; 6.
    - Local 236F Strike, September 5, 1952-April 16, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      - James Matles to Sterling Neal, September 5, 1952; 1.
      - Neal to Ernest DeMaio, September 29, 1952; 2.
      - Matles Memo to David Ratner, October 14, 1952; 3.
      - Matles Memo to Albert Fitzgerald, February 17, 1953; 4.
      - Matles Memo to David Scribner, February 17, 1953; 5.
      - Neal to Julius Emspak, March 25, 1953; 6.
      - Emspak to Neal, April 16, 1953; 7-8.
    - Local 236F Per Capita Arrears, March 19-September 14, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 92)
      - James Matles to Sterling Neal, March 19, 1954; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Neal, May 10, 1954; 2.
      - Marie Reed to Emspak, September 14, 1954; 3.
    - Local 236F Correspondence, Report Excerpt and Grievance List, February 7, 1951-March 25, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 93)
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak Regarding District 7 Transfer, February 7, 1951; 1.
      - Stewards Class Outline With January 22, 1953, Utley Vincent Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, January 1953; 2.
      - Basil Pollitt to David Scribner Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 27, 1953; 3.
      - Grievances Arbitration List, January 20, 1954; 4.
      - James Wright Report Excerpt Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, December 31, 1954; 5.
      - Sterling Neal to James Matles Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry and Per Capita, March 25, 1955; 6.